genial.ly 2019-12-22

# Genially Privacy Policy

Last updated May 24, 2018.

This webpage is property of GENIALLY WEB SL, CIF: B56019912; Registered Office: PLAZA RAMÓN Y CAJAL, 4, 4º CP 14003 Córdoba, Spain; Telephone: +34 957 612 920 / +34 633 011 046; Email: info@genial.ly, support@genial.ly

Registered in the Commercial Register of Córdoba, Book 2154, Sheet 51, number CO-35517, registration 1ª - C.I.F. B-56019912.

### 1\. Right to information.

The privacy policy of GENIALLY WEB SL (henceforth GENIALLY) provides information about how GENIALLY collects personal data and how it uses that data. Although we believe that our focus when processing personal data is fair and reasonable, review this document carefully. We want to ensure that we are fully transparent about how this data is used.

The current policy of data protection regulates the access and use of the service of the Website www.genial.ly that GENIALLY makes available to Internet Users interested in its services and tools for the creation of content.

This Webpage is subject to the norms exclusively applicable in Europe, and both nationals and foreigners who use the Web are subject to it, and hereafter to the Law 34/2002, of the 11th of July, of Societal Services of Information and Electronic Commerce and the REGULATION (EU) 2016/679 OF THE EUROPEAN PARLIAMENT AND COUNCIL of the 27th of April of 2016 in relation to the protection of natural persons regarding the treatment of personal data and the free circulation of this data under current legislation.

In conformance with what is established by the current laws and regulations, GENIALLY WEB SL, owner of the Website, informs the user of this site of the existence of a database of personal nature created by GENIALLY under its responsibility.

Access to our Web page by USERS is free, and for PREMIUM USERS it is contingent upon the contract and the payment of the contracted service.

Both access points are contingent upon the previous reading and complete explicit and unqualified acceptance of the present GENERAL TERMS OF USE in place from the moment of access and which we ask that you read thoroughly.

The users guarantee and answer to the truthfulness, exactness, authenticity and current nature of the personal data provided.

The provision of personal information by the user through our online portal requires a minimum age of 14, or sufficient legal capacity to contract, by virtue of the legislation of Current Protection of Personal Data. In the case of a user under 14, the legal guardian of the minor will be responsible for the use and access that's carried out through our website.

We can, at any time, modify the presentation and configuration of our Web, increase or reduce services, and even remove it as well as borrowed services and content from the Internet.

Confidentiality and security are primary values of GENIALLY and, as a consequence, we take on the commitment to guarantee the privacy of our Users at all times and to not collect unnecessary information.

Down below, we provide you with all the necessary information about our Privacy Policy in relation to the personal data we collect in compliance with article 10 of the Law 34/2002, of the 11th of July, of the services of the Societal Services of Information and Electronic Commerce (LSSICE) and article 13 of the RGPD 2016/679 of the EUROPEAN PARLIAMENT AND COUNCIL of the 27th of April of 2016 concerning the protection of natural persons with regards to the treatment of personal data and the free circulation of that data, and we inform you of the content of this Treatment, specifying:

  * Who is in charge of the processing or treatment of your data.
  * For what purpose do we gather the data we request.
  * What is the legal basis (legitimation) for your treatment: Consent
  * Conservation Period of your personal data
  * In the case of Transfer: To which recipients will your data be disclosed.
  * What are your rights.

### 2\. Overseer of the Treatment of Protection of Personal Data

GENIALLY WEB SL, CIF: B56019912; Registered Office: PLAZA RAMÓN Y CAJAL, 4, 4º CP 14003 Córdoba, Spain; Telephone: +34 957 612 920 / +34 633 011 046; Email: info@genial.ly, support@genial.ly

GENIALLY implements two kinds of Treatments, which comply with current regulations on data protection and ensure that the data you provide is treated legally and securely.

  1. USERS, for those users registered with the service through a free account for which we request an email and password to provide access to free services. The User can be asked for additional information about his or her profile, with a merely statistical goal (education, enterprise, digital content) and to direct the User to the content that most closely fits his or her profile in conformance with the foreseen use of the tools to create content (professor, student, administration, designer, etc.).
  2. PREMIUM USERS, for those users registered with the service through the acquisition of a Premium account, through a paid subscription, treated as clients and who are asked for, along with their email, other basic identification data used to manage the commercial and fiscal relationship. The additional information that is asked for with merely statistical goals and to know the user's profile (teacher, student, etc.)

### 3\. Obligation to provide us with your personal data and the consequences of not doing so.

The personal data requested is necessary to manage your subscription and/or provide the services of creation of content and/or those services associated with the commercial and administrative activity (Premium Users) of GENIALLY. Therefore, if you don't provide this information to us, we will not be able to give you access to the subscription application or offer you the service your have requested.

#### THE TYPE OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT.

We collect Usage Data (that as such does not contain personal data or other personal identifying information) and Personal Data.

Usage data. When you use the GENIALLY service our servers (that can be stored by a third-party provider) can collect information indirectly and automatically (through, for example, the use of your "IP address") about your activity while you visit our website, including the web pages you view and the number of times you view them and information about the browser you are using. We use this browsing information for internal ends, such as to help us understand how websites are being used and to improve it, and also to system administration ends. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when it uses Internet. In some cases, its IP address remains the same from the browsing session until the following session with the browser; but if you use an Internet access provider, your IP address will likely vary from one session to another.

Generally, the usage data does not contain personal information. However, in some cases, the usage data may be stored along with your personal data in such a way that the usage data can also be considered personal data. In these cases, we handle the data in accordance with the provisions of this Privacy Policy.

Personal data and personally identifiable information (”Personal Data”). In some circumstances we can also collect Personal Data, such as your name and address. This could occur upon you registering as a user of the Genially service. In such cases, what type of personal data we ask you to provide will be clearly indicated, and that Personal Data will be stored and processed in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We consider the protection of user privacy a very important principle. We understand clearly that you and your information are one of our priorities. We store and process your personal data (if received) in computers located in the United States or in the EU that are protected by physical and technological security devices. Using the GENIALLY service, you give GENIALLY your consent to store, process, and transfer your personal information (if received) outside of your country of residence within the United States or EU.

If you do not wish to allow your personal information (if existing) to be transferred or used in this way, please do not use the GENIALLY service.

We do not collect personal data from persons under 14 years of age. If you are under 14, do not use any feature of the GENIALLY service that requires you to provide your personal information.

### 4\. Purpose, legitimacy, storage periods

The data of the users registered through the contact form provided for this purpose on the Website is gathered by GENIALLY to facilitate the provision of the services that GENIALLY offers through said Website.

We use the information we collect for the purposes of providing and developing the Genially service. Some of the features our service offers may rely on the use of information we have collected from you in order to ensure that a given feature is customized and targeted for your specific use.

#### USER REGISTRATION FORM

Purpose: Facilitate a means with which you can apply for registration and activate your User account to be able to use and create content with the tools that the platform offers as long as you indicate this information in the corresponding spaces and mark the subscription box.

Legal Basis: The consent of the user when registering through our registration form and the marking of the acceptance box on the terms of use and privacy policy.

Conservation: Once your request is resolved through our form or answered via email, and no new requests or questions are submitted, your data will be erased when you request that it be eliminated.

#### USER SUPPORT FORM

Purpose: Facilitate a means through which you can get in touch with us and receive information related to your registration, use of the platform, and receive information about our services via electronic means (Email) or through chat as long as you indicate this information in the corresponding spaces and mark the subscription box.

Legal Basis: The consent of the user when registering through our registration form and the marking of the acceptance box on the terms of use and privacy policy.

Conservation: Once your request is resolved through our form or answered via email, and no new requests or questions are submitted, your data will be erased when you request that it be eliminated.

(In the case of Premium users, with a current commercial relationship, the time of conservation of their data will be the time legitimized by the commercial relationship itself, through a services contract and according to how long it lasts).

#### APPLICATION FORM_WORK WITH US

Purpose: to inform you about employment offers and open selection processes and offer you a way of contacting us in the case that you are interested in the vacancies that arise in our organization.

Legal Basis: The consent of the user in getting in contact with us through the email provided and authorizing the processing of his or her data as a Candidate in the moment he or she sends the electronic request through the acknowledgment of receipt.

Conservation: The data provided will be conserved until the assignment of a job position or until you exercise your right to cancel within a year.

### 5\. Recipients of your data

GENIALLY uses third-party services ("Providers of data storage, databases, communication and support services, or payment management") to be able to provide the best service possible to our users. The integration with said providers involves the access to data linked to their accounts, limited exclusively to the ability to use the service.

Apart from the Providers of services that are integrated in the tool, GENIALLY, does not reveal its Personal Data to third parties unless:

  1. You have given us your explicit consent to do it;
  2. Except when a legal obligation exists.

### 6\. Rights in relation to your personal data

Anyone can withdraw their consent in any moment when they have allowed for the processing of their data. In no case shall the withdrawal of this consent condition the execution of the services contract or relationships generated previously.

You can exercise the following rights:

  * Request access to your personal data or its correction when it is inexact.
  * Request its elimination when, among other reasons, the data is no longer necessary for the purposes it was collected for.
  * Request the limitation of its processing in certain circumstances.
  * Request to oppose the treatment and processing of your data for reasons related to your particular situation.
  * Request the portability of the data in cases provided for in the current regulations.
  * Other rights recognized by the applicable regulations.

Where and how to request your Rights: Through writing directed at the overseer via their address or email address (indicated in section 2. Overseer of Treatment of Protection of Personal Data), indicating the reference "Personal Data", specifying the right that you wish to exercise and what personal data you wish to exercise it with.

In the case of disagreements with the company in relation to the treatment of your data, you can file a claim before the Authority of Data Protection (www.agpd.es).

### 7\. Security of your personal data

With the goal of safeguarding the security of your personal information, we inform you that we have adopted all the measures of a technical and organizational nature necessary to guarantee the security of personal data provided from being altered, lost, or treated or accessed without authorization.

GENIALLY uses the standard security mechanisms of the industry to protect the information stored in the Register of Users. The personal data and security copies are stored in protected databases situated behind a firewall and with physical and software control access points.

### 8\. Cookies Policy

GENIALLY Uses cookies to offer better final functionality to the users of the GENIALLY service, such as the ability to calculate statistics related to the use of the service. Cookies allow us to record, for example, various user preferences and to calculate user statistics uniquly related to the use of the GENIALLY service.

When using the GENIALLY service, there are times that you may also be exposed to cookies from third parties like Facebook, Google, and other third-party service providers with which GENIALLY can be used. GENIALLY cannot be responsible for how these third-party cookies are used and you can consult the privacy policies of these third parties to obtain more information about how they use cookies.

So, when you access our web, in compliance with article 22 of the Law of Societal Services of Information, we have requested your consent for its use.

We inform you that you can activate or deactivate these cookies by following the instructions of your Internet browser:

  * Chrome: Settings -> Show advanced options -> Privacy -> Content settings.
  * Firefox: Tools -> Options -> Privacy -> History -> Personalized Settings.
  * Internet Explorer: Tools -> Internet Options -> Privacy -> Settings.
  * Safari: Preferences -> Security.
  * Opera: Tools -> Preferences -> Edit preferences -> Cookies
  * Edge: Settings -> See advanced settings -> Privacy and services -> Cookies

For more information, you can consult the Help section of your browser or the support pages:

  * Chrome: support.google.com
  * FireFox: support.mozilla.org
  * Internet Explorer: windows.microsoft.com
  * Safari: http://www.apple.com
  * Opera: http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/
  * Edge: https://privacy.microsoft.com/es-es/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy

### 9\. Updating of your information

It is important that, so that we can keep your personal data updated, you let us know when there has been a change in this information. Otherwise, we will not be held liable for its correctness.

We are not responsible for the privacy policy with respect to the personal data that can third parties may gather through the links available on our web page.

The current Privacy Policy can be modified to adapt itself to the changes produced on our web, such as legislative or case law changes about personal data that arise, and which must be read each time you provide us with your data through this Web.

### 10\. Changes to the current privacy policy

GENIALLY reserves the right to change the current policy to adapt it to the legislative changes or jurisprudence that arise in the future.
